This is Satya Prakash. Well,
he has a grocery store in the market and his life,
but he balances everything from the shop to his family,
so he has two secretaries.
Prakash ji is a complete family man
because he is as concerned about the
health and future of his family as he is
about his business. Therefore,
this Jayprakash ji believes in investing as
little as possible on himself and the most on his business and family.
Just a few days ago, Satya ji had
gone to the Customer Service Center (CSC) to pay his electricity bill. There, a bailiff
told him about health insurance, which Satya ji, as usual,
ignored. Satya ji believes
that as far as health is concerned, as long as work is done, the
information is followed. But the matter did
not work out. Satya Prakash ji had a stomach
ache. A test revealed kidney stones, and
his entire savings were spent on operations
and hospital expenses. Therefore, if you want to keep your
family safe, then first
insure your own health with HDFC and its Arogya
Sanjivani policy. This is the
best health insurance policy that
everyone should have.  The most important
thing is that it provides you and your family with
maximum coverage at minimal cost.
You get hospital expenses
like room rent and ICU
fees, doctor or surgeon fees, diagnostic procedures and other
treatment expenses.
New-age procedures
include robotic surgery and chemotherapy, cataract surgery, and many other procedures mentioned in this
policy. The age limit for taking this policy is also from 3
months to 45 years. This is a
Badshah policy that allows you to
choose between individual and fuller options. This policy has a
waiting period of 30 days and waiting periods of
24 and 48 days for specific diseases. The
available sum insured options range from Rs 3 lakh to Rs
10 lakh. Not only this, if you
wish, plans ranging from Rs 3
lakh to Rs 10 lakh are also available in multiples of Rs 50,000. When
you choose plans like this, you
get better customer service and
faster settlement of claims. A network of more than 10,000 cashless
hospitals, available 24 hours a day.  10,000 rupees in
price-related coincidences on the phone and
why five percent was found is bone, along with the
trust of more than 1.5 crore customers and a big dip in every state which is
always there to help you.